

# DAVID UKO BRADFORD

07032145887 | E: davidbradforduko@yahoo.com, bradforddavid082@gmail.com NO 3 Atani Close, Area 1 Section 2, Garki, Abuja, Nigeria.

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

Github: https://github.com/deviator53

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/david-bradford-651769160/

Portfolio: https://david-bradford.vercel.app

# PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

David is a Motivated IT Professional with 3 years of progressive experience in the Web Development industry. Offering expertise in HTML, CSS, and JAVASCRIPT, with aptitude in Troubleshooting. An energetic self-starter and team builder able to navigate high-stress situations and achieve goals on time and under budget.

### SKILLS 0

- NextJS
- Microsoft Excel
- GraphQL
- NodeJS, ExpressJS
- MongoDB
- Tailwind CSS

- Fluent in Html, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript
- ReactJS
- React Native
- Material UI
- Googling

### **WORK HISTORY**

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

02/2022 to TILL DATE

## ALAN TURING CODES | Wuse Zone 2, Abuja, Nigeria

- Wrote and implemented efficient code.
- Worked closely with other developers, UX designers, business and systems analysts.

## **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER**

08/2021 to TILL DATE

## WAAW FOUNDATION | MKK Plaza, Jabi, Abuja, Nigeria

- Wrote and implemented efficient code.
- Worked closely with other developers, UX designers, business and systems analysts.
- Researched, designed, implemented, and managed software programs.

### **IT CONSULTANT**

07/2020 to 02/2021

## BODEK FADAMA USERS CO-OP SOCIETY | Area 1, Garki, Abuja, Nigeria

- Conduct all IT Operations, maintained and installed all systems.
- Provided support to all help desk operations and managed all products according to customer requirements and provided support to all internal and external customers.

#### **SYSTEM SUPPORT ENGINEER**

04/2018 to 09/2019

### SOFTRUST TECHNOLOGIES LIMITED | Area 11, Garki, Abuja, Nigeria

- Managed and monitored all installed systems and infrastructure to ensure the highest level of availability.
- Monitored and tested application performance to identify potential bottlenecks, develop solutions, and collaborate with developers on solution implementation.
- Provided 2nd and 3rd level technical support and troubleshooting to internal and external clients.

## **NYSC (IT SUPPORT)**

10/2016 to 10/2017

# INDEPENDENT NATIONAL ELECTORAL COMMISSION (INEC) | Calabar, Cross River, Nigeria

- Researched and updated all required materials needed for firm and partners.
- Worked directly with the ICT Department of INEC to achieve Voters Registration.

#### INDUSTRIAL TRAINEE

07/2015 to 11/2015

### FEDERAL MINISTRY OF TRADE AND INVESTMENT | Garki, Abuja, Nigeria

 Supported Federal Ministry of Trade and Investment in improving operations and resolving issues to deliver top-notch service.

#### **EDUCATION** •

Masters of Science | Information Technology
NATIONAL OPEN UNIVERSITY, ABUJA, NIGERIA

NYSC Discharge Certificate

National Youth Service Corps, CROSS-RIVER, NIGERIA

Bachelor of Science | Information Communication Technology 2016

**NOVENA UNIVERSITY OGUME, DELTA, NIGERIA** 

# PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

- Certificate in Mobile Apps Development and Entrepreneurship(UNESCO YOUTH MOBILE)
- Certificate of Completion in Andela Google Africa Scholarship Front End Course
- Certificate in Computer Desktop Publishing
- Professional Diploma in Java Programming with International Institute of Computer Science and Engineering (IICSE)

#### REFERENCES O

**AVAILABLE ON REQUEST** 

2019

2017